Early in the morning, the water will be put into the pond near Behasan.
No, it is not that all the children will be found.   Hey,
eat some paratha.
Oh mother.  You eat the parantha now.  I will be
late because of the paratha.  Hey, at least take your lunch with you.
I am packing it right now.  I will take
lunch today.  Samosa
and laddu will be distributed in school today.  Laddu Samosa?
Happy about what?  Stay here happily till 15th August.   Please bring some
for me too.  Yes, you
make me a beggar of attachment.
[Music]
Nonu oh Nonu hey come quickly friend we're getting late.   It has come, it has come.   All three of you
also took the dupattas from the gallery.
Hey, which dupatta?
Hey, those who want to fly in the air on the song Desh Rangeela.
Well friend, I have only one white one.
But you will bring all three of them.
Friend, I thought I will ask someone in the street for green and orange.
But I never found it on anyone.
Hey friend, where will I tell madam now?  And where will I say that I will say that I did
not get it and said that I can do it
now to the
limit friend, you have
no passion for competition, go run and get the bag,
okay I am coming
and brother take the dupatta also, hey
friend what should I do now, I will ask for the green and orange
dupatta
from Premchand uncle's shop, I will
return them later, hey come quickly, I have come
quickly, I have
kept it, yes that is
right,
I am saying that the orange and green dupatta, what to do
now,
what to do now, I will go and get
both the dupattas from Premchand uncle's shop.
I don't have a single rupee in the shop.
Hey, who is asking for money?  I have my
own solution for free.
But where did your school tie go?
Friend, today I got the school's one so I used the one from the previous
school.
Give me your mouth.   If
I don't give it to you, I will
kill you.  Give it to me.   I am
giving it.   Don't
show it.  [laughter]
Oh man, we're late.   I am
late because of you.
Well, you got late because of me.  Firstly, I was
saved from being humiliated in front of the entire class.   On
top of that, attachment is making me feel bad.  You can just say thank you.   Okay,
fine.  Thank you.  Now at least take a
look inside.  I wonder if the teacher is coming.  We have to go inside now.
No one is coming.  You follow me.
I move forward.  Ok?  Easy.
[MUSIC]
Turned back.
Yes, then who will tell the children what tomorrow holds?
Ma'am [music]
Shivam, tell me what's tomorrow?
Ma'am, tomorrow is Saturday.
Hey mom it's
Saturday.  It's Saturday.  It's Saturday.
Tomorrow is Saturday.  Sit down.  It's Saturday [music].
Hey, Independence Day is tomorrow, 15th August.  So
ma'am can I dance on Yashoda?
No no, is
this the time to come to school?
Ma'am, you had said that we have to buy elections for 15th August,
so I had gone to buy them.
Okay, go and sit on your seat.
Good morning madam ji.
This is good morning.  It's about to be good afternoon.
Hey madam, it's already 9:00.
How late are you?  First period is about to end.
Hey, whatever has started now will end.
What are you talking about?  There is something to be
irritated about here too.  [laughter]
Okay, so stand outside with your hands up until this period is over.
How are they like that?  There
you made me sit on the seat and I had to stand outside with my
hands raised, both of them have come in the gallery only.
He had gone to prepare for the 15th August dance, that's why he is
late.
Why are you late?
Hey madam, I alone went to get the dupattas for the rest of the girls.   So
how did he come first?
Now he came running back and how did he come?
I am coming slowly.
Go and sit on your seat.  Naughty girl.
All the children who are performing dance,
come and meet me in the fifth class.
[MUSIC]
First,
move aside.  O liar,
I came before you, move back.
Hey, you should come first to school too.
Tomorrow I will sweep and mop your face properly
[laughs]
for now, if you go, I will mop your face.
At least the barber will wash you.
Hey, I will wash you. I am telling you, move back.
O Soniye, Jatna, don't stay back. I will
break your butt. Move away,
who is making so much noise? It's
madam ji,
oh mother,
what are you doing here, come to your class
and you also go to your class.
Madam, you yourself called the dance
children to come to the fifth class.
Okay, yes, come.
Ma'am, you had invited me also to your dance, I am here.
Yes brother, you also come.
Come on, tell me the song.  I love India.   Of
both.
Ma'am, I have been practicing dance for the last two weeks.
Madam ji is lying.  I have been practicing my friend
's song for a month.
We decided on the song.  Dance for a minute.
Ma'am music?   You've been
practicing for two weeks,
you need music for this.  Do it like this.
Do one thing Bijli, you sing and I will show you my dance.
Yes, if you just kick me, I will become Tansen.
Stand there and dance, Shanti.  [laughter]
This world,
this bride,
this world, this bride, this bride.  I
love my India.  I love my India.
[laughter] You've just been
practicing for two weeks, is this some kind of
dance?  Do one thing little one, go on the road.
Oye Maa
Maam I will dance on Nanna Munna Rahi.
Make him dance on Nanna Munna Rahi.   I will slap you and turn you
around, why would I do this
?
Go to your class.
Yes son.  Tell me your name.
Bijli and Nonu.
Bijli and Nonu.  You have one more dance,
right?  Did you get the dupatta?
Yes madam, I have taken the dupatta.  Took all three.   That's
ok.  Take it to your class.
Ok.
Ma'am, Principal Sir has sent a notice that the
Independence Day function which is to be held tomorrow has been cancelled.
Ok.   It's
great.  Tomorrow I will sleep comfortably at home with the sheets spread out.   I am
Nanna Munna Rai.  I am a soldier of the country.   I am
Nanna Munna Rai.  I am a soldier of the country.
You also speak with me.  Jai Hind.
These these these boys, boys will dance, boys
will dance, boys are
dancing, what does it mean, is there any
problem,
boys are dancing, it means boys are dancing, tell me
in Hindi, I am not able to understand, should I
say it in English, I
understand Hindi also and your intentions
too, do
n't talk about intentions, which of your rotten
steps have I come to steal, which
dance step, you have stolen the entire song, friend, hey,
which song did you steal, are you crazy, don't
show us,
we were practicing dance for two weeks.  I was
late just in getting my name registered.
So who is at fault here?  It's yours.  I should have got my
name registered earlier.  Wow, he is doing just one step on such a good song.
I love my
India.
[laughter]
Hey, what new thing did you guys do?
You people are also going on beating me up.
Oh ho, now this old uncle will tell you
where we have surrounded the new place.
Old Uncle, have you seen yourself in the mirror?   She
looks old.
My glasses are looking good and my face looks blind.
You must have been seen.  Are?  Old man, do
I look cute? Look carefully, I will
mute it in one rapid.
Okay, hey, hey,
leave it, what is happening,
Madam ji has
stolen all this, song, song,
song. Hey, tomorrow's function has been cancelled
and it is still half day. Everyone go home.
Madam ji, you will get laddus and samosas, right?
Yes, you must be meeting them at the gate, go and get them.
Where are they like this?   Yes.
Hey, we want samosas.  Give me samosas.
Samosas are only for teachers.  It is not for you people.
What are these things?  We are paying the fees.
Samosas are being fed to the teachers.   Yes.
Sir's order.  Samosas are only
for teachers.
Hey, there has been a robbery.  I got looted in the crowded market
[music] I got looted
in the crowded market oh I got
looted in the
shop walk for me,
I just keep saying this, oh he won't bite me, he won't
bite me, come on
oh mother sorry bhaiya don't be afraid, don't be
afraid, put the roti up, he will eat it,
prop is over [laughs] keep the dupatta, write write write write write write, I have written it, yes yes I have kept it, this is
good, I will get the next dialogue from the neighbour.
Speak quickly.  Otherwise we will go out there.
What a dirty acting you have done brother.  But Sir, I
slipped your buffalo's eye.  The corpse hurried quickly quickly quickly.
This was another dialogue.
Which scarf?
Hey, which one?
What was it?
Yes.  I can't speak my dialogue, friend.
This is a video from Delhi.  Idea.   Don't
move or retreat.  Sony, I will
break the leash.  Be behind.  You have
completely pressed my hand, Bhas's eye, you know,
dance, do it
brother, what is he asking, do it, yes, okay, okay, no, no,
do it properly, it is fine, you have taken the
white scarf, but I am saying,
oh, now this old uncle will tell you where did we change it, oh,
now this old uncle will tell you where did we change it,
Raja, you are blind, you will be able to see, give
me the stick.
Two,
you stay here for a while, won't you?  No, you are not following behind.   Am
I here?
Yes.
So, are you looking here now?
Yes.  So at least I will be able to see it like this.
Get into the act.
Oh, it took a long time.   My
love, I met red people.  How all of them
?  I know you guys must be absolutely taut
because you are taut and I am taut, yes
brother, today is 15th August, okay, on 15th August
our school will be cheated a lot by the
principal and teachers, friend,
we prepared our dance performance for the whole month and
you came to the school and said that now there is a
holiday for the next day, go and enjoy and then when it was time to
distribute laddus and samosas, you gave
us those boondis, you gave us boondis, is it
any big deal, the fees are huge and we should get boondis
and to those whom you are paying,
giving money, you should give laddus and samosas to those teachers.
Meaning, where are you making mistakes
Anshu?  Yes, I have been cheated a lot.  This wo
n't work.  Ok.  Otherwise, if this
ever happens to your girlfriend, then like the video
and tell her in the comments that yes, I am not
alone.  Your girl, this happened.
Your throat was also deceived.  Otherwise, go
follow me on Instagram.  Share the video on
everyone's phone and wait for the next video
because the next video is about to come, it will be a very
strong video, okay because I have a
lot of time to make the next video,
I just spent it pampering you and thought that
yes, I will make the video quickly,
our video will be a small one but the next
video will be very strong, so till then, on
my behalf, thank you all, Jai Hind, Jai Bharat and love you Mane [
Music] Re Mane Re Mane Re Mane Re
No Nanhi Jaan Chhoda Seena